Shoot first. Sightsee later.
In Bruges is a comedy, drama, crime film directed by Martin McDonagh.
Ray and Ken, two hit men, are in Bruges, Belgium,
waiting for their next mission.
While they are there they have time to think and
discuss their previous assignment.
When the mission is revealed to Ken, it is not what he expected.
Ray, played by Colin Farrell.
Ken, played by Brendan Gleeson.
Harry, played by Ralph Fiennes.
Chloë, played by Clémence Poésy.
Marie, played by Thekla Reuten.
Jimmy, played by Jordan Prentice.
In Bruges is a 2008 black comedy-drama crime thriller film directed and
written by Martin McDonagh in his feature-length debut.
It stars Colin Farrell and Brendan Gleeson as two London-based Irish
hitmen hiding in Bruges, with Ralph Fiennes as their boss.
The film is set and was filmed in Bruges, Belgium.
In Bruges was the opening night film of the 2008 Sundance Film Festival and
opened in limited release in the United States on 8 February 2008.
It garnered a box office of $34.5 million.
For his performance in the film, Farrell won the Golden Globe Award for Best Actor – Motion
Picture Musical or Comedy, while Gleeson was nominated in the same category.
McDonagh won the BAFTA Award for Best Original Screenplay and was
nominated for the Academy Award in the same category.
The film explores themes of drug dealer, hitman,
tourist, dark comedy, bruges, belgium.
The tone is lighthearted and dark and emotional.